Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 73, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The GE Approach to Employee Relations and Union Relations, 1964; Publication (Box 73, Folder 20)
    Author: Philip D. Moore
- Box: 73, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: PoliticsThe Businessman's Biggest Job in 1958, Publication (Box 73, Folder 21)
- Box: 73, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Manpower in General Electric Planning for the Future, 1965; Publication (Box 73, Folder 22)
    Notes: Includes; Manpower Planning, Manpower Planning in Louisville, Manpower Planning in Evendale, Employment Security in Philadelphia, Special Manpower Planning Problems at Clock and Timer Department, and Manpower Plannig Summary.
- Box: 73, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A Study of the Performance Appraisal Interview, 1963; Publication (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Box: 73, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A Study of the Threat and Participation in an Industrial Performance Appraisal Program, 1963; Publication (Box 73, Folder 24)
    Author: E. Kay, J.R.P. French, H.H. Meyer
- Box: 73, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Statement on the Walsh-Healy Safety and Health Regulations, 1964; Publication (Box 73, Folder 25)
    Notes: March 20, 1964
- Box: 73, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Increasing Management Effectiveness Through Work Planning, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 26)
- Box: 73, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Take a new Look at Performance Appraisal, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 27)
    Author: Marion Kellogg
    Notes: September 1964
  - Item 2: Manager Development: The Critical Factor in Corporate Progress, Publication (Box 73, Folder 27)
    Author: Richard J. Anton
    Notes: August 3, 1965
- Box: 73, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Plans, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 28)
    Notes: April 11, 1966
- Box: 73, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Management Development Methods, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 29)
- Box: 73, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Personnel Research, 1961; Publication (Box 73, Folder 30)
- Box: 73, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Personnel Reseach: Description of PRS-Produced Materials Available to Members of Management of the Du Pont Company, 1960; Publication (Box 73, Folder 31)
    Notes: Reviewed January 1960
- Box: 73, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Employee Evaluation, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 32)
    Author: W.L. Stabler
- Box: 73, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1959; Publication (Box 73, Folder 33)
    Notes: March 13, 1957
- Box: 73, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: A New Plant in Town, 1958; Publication (Box 73, Folder 34)
    Author: Robert L. Hershey
    Notes: July 11, 1958
- Box: 73, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Selection Procedure for Supervisory Potential, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 35)
- Box: 73, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Technical Graduates in Technical Activities, 1959; Publication (Box 73, Folder 36)
    Notes: March 31, 1956
- Box: 73, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Yerkes Rayon News, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 37)
    Notes: November 5, 1952
- Box: 73, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Application for Employment, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 38)
- Box: 73, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Report on Employee, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 39)
- Box: 73, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Instructions for Employee Appraisal, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 40)
- Box: 73, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Report on Employee: Performance Review, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 41)
- Box: 73, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 73, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Personal Records, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 42)
- Box: 73, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 73, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Personal Adjustments Among Retired Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 43)
    Notes: July 19, 1954
- Box: 73, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 73, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: A Pension Study Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 73, Folder 44)
- Box: 73, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 73, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Management Development Ideas: How Dr. Pepper Trains Route-Riding Supervisors, 1958; Publication (Box 73, Folder 45)
- Box: 73, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 73, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Our Social Responsibilities, 1968; Publication (Box 73, Folder 46)
    Notes: June 3, 1968
- Box: 73, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 73, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart: Employee Relations Department, 1969; Publication (Box 73, Folder 47)
- Box: 73, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 73, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Du Pont Employee Relocation Policy, 1969; Publication (Box 73, Folder 48)
- Box: 73, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 73, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Stockholders Chart, 1969; Publication (Box 73, Folder 49)
- Box: 73, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 73, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations Department Functional Organization Chart, 1969; Publication (Box 73, Folder 50)
    Notes: Revised October 1, 1968
- Box: 73, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 73, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Industiral Relations Division, 1969; Publication (Box 73, Folder 51)
    Notes: April 1, 1968
- Box: 73, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 73, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Office Supervisory Series: Meeting 9 Delegation of Responsibility, 1959; Publication (Box 73, Folder 52)
- Box: 73, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 73, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Training Within the Du Pont Company, 1960; Publication (Box 73, Folder 53)
- Box: 73, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 73, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Training Within the Du Pont Company, 1962; Publication (Box 73, Folder 54)
- Box: 73, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 73, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Equal Opportunity: A Progress Report, 1969; Publication (Box 73, Folder 55)
- Box: 73, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 73, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Employee Relocation Policy: Administrative Manual, 1969; Publication (Box 73, Folder 56)
    Notes: April, 1969
- Box: 73, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 73, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Plans, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 57)
    Notes: Revised April 13, 1970
- Box: 73, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 73, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations Department Functional Organization Chart, 1971; Publication (Box 73, Folder 58)
    Notes: Revised April 1, 1971
- Box: 73, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 73, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Personnel Development Within the Du Pont Company, 1975; Publication (Box 73, Folder 59)
- Box: 73, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 73, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Management Development Methods, 1975; Publication (Box 73, Folder 60)
- Box: 73, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 73, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: This is Du Pont: The Story of Employment Opportunities, 1954; Publication (Box 73, Folder 61)
- Box: 73, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 73, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: This is Du Pont: The Salesman Story, 1955; Publication (Box 73, Folder 62)
- Box: 73, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 73, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Library of Programmed Instruction Courses: Safety Training, 1971; Publication (Box 73, Folder 63)
- Box: 73, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 73, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: The Blender: Works Engineering Training and Testing Program Now in Full Swing, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 64)
- Box: 73, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 73, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Moonbeams: Programmed Instruction: New Path to New Skills, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 65)
    Notes: July 1966
- Box: 73, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 73, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Developing Supervisory Personnel, 1960; Publication (Box 73, Folder 66)
- Box: 73, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 73, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Library of Programmed Instruction Courses: Vocational Training, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 67)
- Box: 73, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 73, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Orientation of the New Employee, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 68)
- Box: 73, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 73, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Programmed Learning Multiplies Maintenance Manpower, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 69)
    Author: Dr. Arthur C. Santora
- Box: 73, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 73, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Du Pont Organizational Chart, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 70)
    Notes: January 1, 1972
- Box: 73, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 73, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: How to Train Operators Faster and Better, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 71)
    Notes: Reprinted from April 1967
- Box: 73, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 73, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Education and Applied Technology Division, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 72)
- Box: 73, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 73, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: The Story of Safety, 1952; Publication (Box 73, Folder 73)
    Notes: First Printing 1952
- Box: 73, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 73, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Psychological Testing: A Critical Look at This Method in Evaluating People for Jobs, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 74)
    Author: W.R.G. Bender; R.W. Bowers; H.E. Loveless
    Notes: August 1964
- Box: 73, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 73, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Studies in Employee Thinking and Feeling; Ten Years Company Experience in Conducting Employee Surveys, 1966; Publication (Box 73, Folder 75)
    Author: W.R.G. Bender
    Notes: April 1959
- Box: 73, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 73, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: This is Du Pont: Automation and Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 73, Folder 76)
- Box: 73, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 73, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Professional Development in the Engineering Department of the Du Pont Company, 1964; Publication (Box 73, Folder 77)
- Box: 73, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 73, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: The Scientist as a Person, 1962; Publication (Box 73, Folder 78)
    Notes: November 1958
- Box: 73, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 73, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Management Development Methods, 1960; Publication (Box 73, Folder 79)
- Box: 73, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 73, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Organizing for Plant Start-up, 1960; Publication (Box 73, Folder 80)
- Box: 73, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 73, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: The Orientation of New Employees, 1960; Publication (Box 73, Folder 81)
- Box: 73, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 73, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Management Morale: Delaware Chemical Symposium, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 82)
- Box: 73, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 73, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Introduction of New Man, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 83)
- Box: 73, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 73, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart: Works Technical Section - Yerkes Plant, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 84)
    Notes: November 1, 1952
- Box: 73, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 73, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Management Morale, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 85)
    Notes: March 31, 1954
- Box: 73, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 73, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Contributory Group Life Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 86)
    Notes: Originally adopted: May 1, 1952; Last Amended: January 1, 1957
- Box: 73, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 73, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Du Pont Tuition Refund Program, Publication (Box 73, Folder 87)
- Box: 73, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 73, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Can We Avoid A Crisis In Resources, 1972; Publication (Box 73, Folder 88)
    Author: Charles B. McCoy
    Notes: December 4, 1972
- Box: 73, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 73, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Adjusting the Disabled to Gainful Employment, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 89)
    Author: Niel E. Eckelberry
    Notes: January 19, 1955
- Box: 73, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 73, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company Organizational Chart, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 90)
    Notes: January 14, 1955
- Box: 73, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 73, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Con Edison Employment Office, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 91)
    Notes: Employment Recruiting
- Box: 73, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 73, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison System Medical Form, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 92)
- Box: 73, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 73, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Staten Island is Merged; Other Organization Changes, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 93)
    Notes: Merged on December 31
- Box: 73, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 73, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: A 10-Year Evaluation of a Job Rotation Executive Development Program, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 94)
    Author: D.S. Sargent
    Notes: April 1952
- Box: 73, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 73, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Executive Inventory and Development Briefing Session; American Management Association Job Rotation, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 95)
    Author: Dwight S. Sargent
    Notes: May 28, 1952
- Box: 73, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 73, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Form, 1956; Publication (Box 73, Folder 96)
- Box: 73, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 73, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: An Address Presented at the Schenectady Section of the American Society of Mechanical Engineers on "Executive Development", 1954; Publication (Box 73, Folder 97)
    Notes: Mach 19, 1953
- Box: 73, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 73, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Are Greybeards White Elephants, 1952; Publication (Box 73, Folder 98)
    Author: John J. Wittmer
- Box: 73, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 73, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. Breif Outline of Employee Benefits, 1967; Publication (Box 73, Folder 99)
    Notes: January 1, 1967
- Box: 73, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 73, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Around the System, 1973; Publication (Box 73, Folder 100)
    Author: Louis H. Roddis, Jr.; Walter A. Morris, Jr.; James G. Stark
    Notes: March 1973
- Box: 73, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 73, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Co. of New York Inc. Corporate Organization, 1973; Publication (Box 73, Folder 101)
    Notes: January 1, 1973
- Box: 73, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 73, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Management Salary Plan; General Description, 1971; Publication (Box 73, Folder 102)
    Notes: January 1, 1971
- Box: 73, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 73, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Highlights: Con Edison Tuition Aid Program, 1973; Publication (Box 73, Folder 103)
- Box: 73, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 73, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Hire & Higher, 1973; Publication (Box 73, Folder 104)
- Box: 73, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 73, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Atomic Power and Safety, 1955; Publication (Box 73, Folder 105)
- Box: 73, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 73, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. Memorandum: Statement as to Retirement Plan for Employees and Officers, 1950; Publication (Box 73, Folder 106)
    Notes: March 16, 1950
- Box: 73, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 73, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company Organizational Chart, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 107)
    Notes: February 15, 1953
- Box: 73, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 73, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. Memorandum: Rating of Eligible Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 73, Folder 108)
    Notes: September 5, 1950
- Box: 73, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 73, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison System Companies Application for Employment, 1950; Publication (Box 73, Folder 109)
- Box: 73, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 73, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company and Affiliated Companies: Brief Outline of Employee Benefits, 1950; Publication (Box 73, Folder 110)
- Box: 73, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 73, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company of New york, Inc. Memorandum, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 111)
- Box: 73, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 73, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc.: Brief Outline of Employee Benefits, 1953; Publication (Box 73, Folder 112)
- Box: 73, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 73, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc.: Brief Outline of Employee Benefits, 1961; Publication (Box 73, Folder 113)
    Notes: January 1, 1961
- Box: 73, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 73, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Office Supervisory Series: Meeting 1 Productivity Through Good Supervision, 1959; Publication (Box 73, Folder 114)
- Box: 73, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 73, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Office Supervisory Series: Meeting 2 Departmental Employment Interview, 1959; Publication (Box 73, Folder 115)
- Box: 73, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 73, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Borden's Madison Avenue Management Development Program 1958, 1962; Publication (Box 73, Folder 116)
    Author: Earl Bruner, Hoke Simpson
    Notes: March, April, May 1958
- Box: 74, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employees' Progress Report, 1956; Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 1956
  - Item 2: Job Specifications, 1955; Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Notes: Revised September 28, 1955
  - Item 3: Employees' Progress Report (to be Completed by the Employee), 1956; Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Periodic Review of Personnel for Management Development, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: How is He Doing: Composite Summary, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Monthly Investment Plan for the Employees of Florida Power and Light Company, Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Confidential Florida Power & Light Company Periodic Review of Personnel for Management Development, 1971; Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reviewed January 1971
  - Item 8: Florida Power & Light Company Salary Ranges - Job Classifications, Commercial, Financial & Administrative, Operating, Engineering, 1970; Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Notes: November 28, 1970
  - Item 9: Confidential Flordida Power & Light Company Periodic Review of Personnel (To be completed in ink by Employee), Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Confidential Florida Power & Light Company Periodic Review of Personnel (To be completed by Supervisor), Publication (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Box: 74, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: For your Family and Future; Flexonics Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Author: John F. P. Farrar
- Box: 74, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Management Planning, 1965; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Box: 74, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Counseling Subordinates After Performance Review, 1957; Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Box: 74, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Performance Review Program, 1956; Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Box: 74, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Creative Thinking, 1956; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Box: 74, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Some Elements of Industrial Economics, 1956; Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Box: 74, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Management Development Series: Survey of Economic Education, 1954; Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
    Author: Dillard E. Bird
    Notes: Second Printing: February 1952
- Box: 74, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Application for Business Fellowship; College-Business Exchange Program 1957, Publication (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Box: 74, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Fraternal Order of Police Grand Lodge, The only National Police Organization Presents A Survey of 1966 Salaries and Working Conditions of the Police Department in the United States, 1967; Publication (Box 74, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 15, 1966
- Box: 74, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Skill Behind the Man, Publication (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Box: 74, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Better Utilization of College Teaching Resources, 1957; Publication (Box 74, Folder 12)
    Notes: October 1956
- Box: 74, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Never Get Paid Today What You Can Put Off Until Tomorrow, Publication (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Box: 74, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Gates' "Teamwork for Dividends" Program, 1959; Publication (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Box: 74, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Workers' Education Conference, 1946; Publication (Box 74, Folder 15)
    Notes: February 9-11, 1946
- Box: 74, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Fifth Annual Management Conference: Taxation "A Key Element in Social and Economic Life", 1953; Publication (Box 74, Folder 16)
    Author: John J. Mann; Herbert J. Miller; Herbert W. Funk; Fedele F. Fauri; Henry W. Balgooyen; Slade Kendrick; Edward H. Litchfield
    Notes: April 17,18 1953
  - Item 2: You and Cornell, 1969; Publication (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Box: 74, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Job Analysis Program, 1955; Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Suggestion System, 1946; Publication (Box 74, Folder 17)
    Notes: November 1945
- Box: 74, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Safety Department, 1949; Publication (Box 74, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 1949
- Box: 74, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Miscellaneous Provisions, 1960; Publication (Box 74, Folder 19)
- Box: 74, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Journal of Applied Psychology: Influence of Brainstorming Instructions and Problem Sequence on a Creative Problem Solving Test, 1959; Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Author: Arnold Meadow; Sidney J. Parnes; Hayne Reese
    Notes: Received March 16, 1959
  - Item 2: Journal of Educational Psychology: Effects of Extended Effort in Creative Problem Solving, 1961; Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Author: Sidney J. Parnes
    Notes: Received October 3, 1960
  - Item 3: Developments in the Creative Education Movement, Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Author: Alex F. Osborn
  - Item 4: The Board of Directors of the Council for International Progress in Management, Inc. Cordially Invites you to Attend its Annual Reception and Dinner, 1963; Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Notes: January 30, 1963
  - Item 5: Journal of Applied Psychology: Evaluation of Training in Creative Problem Solving, 1959; Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Author: Arnold Meadow; Sidney J. Parnes
    Notes: Received September 3, 1958
  - Item 6: Journal of Educational Psychology: Effects of "Brainstorming" Instructions on Creative Problem Solving by Trained and Untrained Subjects, 1959; Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Author: Sidney J. Parnes and Arnold Meadow
    Notes: Received December 17, 1958
  - Item 7: Compendium of Research on Creative Imagination, Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Author: Sidney J. Parnes; Harold F. Harding
  - Item 8: Evaluation of Persistence of Effects Produced by a Creative Problem-Solving Course, 1960; Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Author: Sidney J. Parnes; Arnold Meadow
  - Item 9: How About the Public?, 1961; Publication (Box 74, Folder 20)
    Notes: Aril 3, 1961
- Box: 74, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Your Job and its Evaluation, 1952; Publication (Box 74, Folder 21)
    Notes: September 1952
  - Item 2: Your Performance and its Evaluation, 1953; Publication (Box 74, Folder 21)
    Notes: March, 1953